all right so yesterday I encountered
game B for the first time and although I
still don't know if I'm able to explain
in this video it has given me the
language to talk about when I've been
doing for the last two years what the
global tech cooperative can give us
which is creating game B from great game
a because anything that is game B has to
come out of game a and game a is our
current competitive game which is called
I call capitalism and so what I'm
talking about dismantling capitalism and
people get defensive this is better
language creating game B out of game a
creating the next thing and I believe
anything that is going to come out to be
more powerful to be game changing and B
have the competitive advantage nearly
right away is to include the masses not
demand the masses aren't included but
always have that invitation open to do
you want to be part of creating this and
having it be as transparent and open as
you can
meaning it has to be intellectually
accessible and financially accessible it
can't be behind technological length a
technical language that you have to have
a degree to be able to understand it
which doesn't mean people to have to
dumb down their language but we have to
be able to own as individuals I don't
understand that I needed to explain to
me because we're all gonna have areas we
don't understand it in and we want
people to come on board and say ok I can
see what has been done before I got here
so I can trust it and I can participate
I can see I can get involved in the
niche that I want to be involved in and
allowing for that allowing that some
people there might be a center group
that we all need to understand certain
speakers certain documentaries and but
mainly it needs to be right no you study
what you're interested in how do we find
the common thread because the system is
too complex we can't all know the same
things we're not all supposed to know
the same things we're supposed to have
our individual complexity
individual uniqueness that adds up into
amazing complexity that that is what we
bring to the table that is why it's omni
wind because each of us is a unique
individual when we bring ourselves to
the table there's something there that
wasn't there before we don't need to
copy us and be clones and have all the
same intellect and the same abilities
and the same challenges it's continually
owning what is challenging how do we how
do we help people create an easier life
how do we help people create a system
they want to participate in it's more
fun and at the same time having the
group of actions that when we
individually do what is simple and
enjoyable together is a mass powerful
powerful stuff gets done that does take
over and so it does out-compete game a
on its own turf so I'm sitting with this
information I also had a three-hour
conversation with my brother today but
it was like labor and how we use a like
the thing we created was like well we
just solved the minute people don't need
to work for minimum wage anymore
the only workers that are gonna be left
outside of the system are basically
basically the government workers and the
ones that are paid really well and we do
it like in all of it we solved it it was
like this is weird now that we can have
language that works for us to have this
conversation and I'm loving this
language and even though I struggle with
new language there's something about
this because they talk about it in
biological terms and economic can and
that I was like most of what like you're
could even eukaryotic and prokaryotic it
was like yeah that was long before
that's knowledge it's in my head I got
that I don't need to learn that I could
learn the little pieces of language to
be able to communicate in this language
with people who are already passionate
about this because game B is the
language that comes like thank you
someone gave it language because that
was the thing I was missing I am not
strong on language and but I'm strong on
the underlying concepts of like how we
actually create this and have struggled
with it it's a little antithesis an
aesthetical a little antithetical to the
actual the game be a concept though to
me everyone's like so no one has the
answer
to co-creator but I do it's what I've
been sitting around and I don't think my
answer is like let's cut and paste it
that's what the answers in the world the
ideas anything has to be dynamic and
changing but I've sat with by myself all
of these questions and come up with a
solution and so I have something to
offer in all of these areas how do we
fund it how do we trust it how do we run
it how do we do all of all of these
things I have a answer and because it's
a cohesive whole these people understand
that those pieces need to be there and
we can make it way better and I can hear
that just I'm so happy to have
encountered this so as for always a
better world is on its way it has never
felt more tangible than it does right
now it is going to be brought to you by
our diversity our diversity of thought
our diversity of emotion or diversity of
individual experiences and challenges
and talents I will see you tomorrow
please like and subscribe hit that
little bell and please join idea cafe
and the fix the world Fridays and be
part of the conversation that is going
to get us to that better world